

GILANG RAMANDA PURBA

https://gilangramandapurba.github.io/

0812 - 7328 - 3614

gramanda35@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/gilang-ramanda-purba/

Prabumulih, Sumatera Selatan

ABOUT ME

I am a graduate of the Bina Darma University in Palembang with an Information Systems study program with basic Web Development (Html, CSS) and am interested in Ui Ux design with (Figma) tools, but also willingly learn any new skills out of that field, I also worked as Quality Assurance.

EDUCATION

• Senior High School 07, Prabumulih, Sumatera Selatan

(2014 - 2017)

Major Social Sciences

Bina Darma University, Palembang, Sumatera Selatan

(2017 - 2021)

Major Information System

WORK EXPERIENCE

Quality Assurance - PT. SRI REJEKI ISMAN.TBK

(Juli 2022 – Januari 2023)

- Carry out ready-to-use production checks with a target 0f 60 pcs within 60 minutes,
- Ensure that the resulting product is by consumer demand,
- Correct or minimize errors during production,
- Carry out apply iso-9001 Iso -1400 standard,
- And play a role in making decisions on production that is not by the standard.

ORGANIZATIONAL EXPERIENCE

HIMSIF (Himpunan Ikatan Mahasiswa Sistem Informasi)

(September 2017 – September 2018)

- Helping to prepare an event event
- Assist future organizational planning
- Assist in thinking of future ideas

Student Outbound ILKOM diUniversiti Selanggor Malaysia

(Januari 2020 - Feburari 2020)

- Conducting discussions between students of ILKOM Universiti Malaysia faculties
- Conducting regional food bazaar activities
- Conducting art and cultural performances in front of Malaysian students

EXPERTISE AND CERTIFICATION

HARD SKILL: Ms.Office (Word, Excell, Power Point), Desain (Canva, Figma), Pemograman (HTML, CSS)

SOFT SKILL: Dissipline, Team Work, Communication

SERTIFIKAT : Cisco Networking Academy, Microsoft Academy Associate (HTML 5), Project Management

Associate, ITP TOEFL TEST 393

DAFTAR RIWAYAT HIDUP

DATA PRIBADI

1. Nama Lengkap : Gilang Ramanda Purba

Tempat & Tanggal lahir : Prabumulih, 17 November 1999
 Alamat : Prabumulih, Sumatera Selatan, 31113

4. Jenis Kelamin : Pria

5. Status Perkawinan : Belum menikah

6. Agama : Kristen

No. Telpon : 0812 - 7328 - 3614
 Email : gramanda35@gmail.com

PENDIDIKAN FORMAL

2006 – 2011 : SD NEGERI 56 KOTA PRABUMULIH
 2011 – 2014 : SMP NEGERI 05 KOTA PRABUMULIH

3. 2014 – 2017 : SMA NEGERI 07 KOTA PRABUMULIH JURUSAN IPS

4. 2017 – 2021 : UNIVERSITAS BINA DARMA PALEMBANG JURUSAN SISTEM

INFORMASI

PENDIDIKAN INFORMAL

1. 2012 : Kursus Bahasa Inggris Budiwijaya Kota Prabumulih

PENGALAMAN KERJA

1. QUALITY ASSURANCE – PT SRI REJEKI ISMAN.TBK

(Juli 2022 – Januari 2023)

- Berperan serta menjaga kualitas dan kuantitas produk
- Berperan serta memperbaiki atau memperkecil kesalahan produk
- Berperan serta mengambil keputusan terhadap produk yang tidak sesuai standar
- Berperan serta mengawasi produk yang dibuat sesuai dengan permintaan costumer
- Berperan serta menjaga reputasi perusahaan

(Gilang Ramanda Purba)